kapdaclick.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | kapdaclick

**Last updated on June 24, 2015**  
Kapdaclick.com wants it’s customers to have the best standards for protected transactions and customer information privacy. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website. When you access the Website, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.1

## 1. Information and Usage

**Privacy Policy** informs how KAPDACLICK gathers personal and non-personal knowledge, classified as voluntary or obligatory and discloses, assists and uses such data through Website. 'Personal Information' is data that can be utilised to singularly identify or network to a person (" **Personal Information** "). Personal Information shall contain detail about your name, telephone number, address, email address and such other data.

You may need to specify KAPDACLICK your Personal Information for using KAPDACLICK, for instance, making a User ID, give data while registering, or provide financial details while making a purchase, upload subject, take part in any online contest or survey, interact with KAPDACLICK's customer service, give reviews for content on Website etc.

KAPDACLICK gathers Personal Information that KAPDACLICK considers to be pertinent and is required to interpret you or your interests.

KAPDACLICK saves your Personal Information to list and expedite your participation in activities, record your interests, to give you a personalized Website experience, to inform you of any revised data and other relevant services offered by KAPDACLICK.

We keep you notified about the current content accessible on Website, offers on products and services of KAPDACLICK, to help you with customer service or technical issues, to follow up with you after your visit and guide your affiliation with KAPDACLICK or restrict fraud use.

To make our Website efficient, some data may be gathered every time you access the Website. Such details may be saved in server logs.

These encrypted statistics do not analyze you personally, but give us details about your visit to Website and the type of user who is visiting the Website and browsing processes by you.

This data may contain: IP address of your server from where the Website is being accessed, the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.), the operating system of your system and the Website you last accessed before visiting our Website.

The period of time of your stay on the Website is saved in the session with the date and time of your visits. This data is used by KAPDACLICK to know the number of user visiting the Website.

Some of the data related to the Website and your visit may be shared by investors, developer, sponsors, strategic business partners, associates and advertisers of KAPDACLICK to enhance our business but we assure that these data will never contain any of your Personal Informations.

This anonymous data is gathered through a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major Websites. When you access the Website, KAPDACLICK's servers may gather data automatically and indirectly regarding your activities on Website by cookies.

A cookie is a minor amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is stored on a user's system hard drive. This anonymous data is held discretely and is not attached to Personal Information submitted by you to KAPDACLICK. You can decide, If you want your web browser to accept cookies or not.

If you haven't varied your computer's settings, more chances are your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can delete your browser cookies or disable them, but this may impact your experience with Website and may make parts of the Website inaccessible , “We recommend that you leave them turned on”.

We use third-party service providers to deliver ads on our behalf over the internet and on this Website. They may gather anonymous data about your access to the Website, and your interaction with our services. No personally identifiable data is used in this process. They do not know the name, address, email address, or any personally identifying data about you.

KAPDACLICK also uses the log file like other website servers which is the standard measures. They include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use them to analyse trends, administer the site, track a user's movement and gather broad demographic data for aggregate use.

“IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable data”

**KAPDACLICK DOES NOT trade or sell your Personal Information in any manner, except as specified herein, or if express consent is sought from you.**

Your Personal Information provided by you is used only:

  1. to alleviate your use of Website;
  2. if you buy any content or avail any service from Website, to complete and fulfil your purchase, for example, to have your payments processed, communicate with you about your purchase and provide you with related customer service;
  3. if you buy any content or avail any service from Website, to complete and fulfil your purchase, for example, to have your payments processed, communicate with you about your purchase and provide you with related customer service;
  4. to help you address your difficulties with the Website, including informing any technical problems;
  5. to reply to your queries or your requests for data about the services;
  6. to supply you with data about KAPDACLICK's products and services and to send you data, materials, and offers from KAPDACLICK;
  7. to send you necessary data about the Website, changes to KAPDACLICK's terms, policies and conditions and/or other administrative data;
  8. to send you marketing communications that KAPDACLICK thinks may be helpful to you;
  9. to personalize your experience on the Website and KAPDACLICK's other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to you;
  10. to direct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website);
  11. to better the content, services and advertising on Website;
  12. to protect the integrity of the Website; and
  13. to respond to judicial process and provide data to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

You acknowledge that apart from your Personal Information, if you upload any content on the Website, such content may contain data including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. “ **KAPDACLICK will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to third parties** “.

  1. KAPDACLICK may reveal collective data about the use of Website, but it will never include Personal Information.
  2. KAPDACLICK does not publish Personal Information to third parties in normal flow of operations.
  3. However, in conditions when KAPDACLICK is legally obligated to reveal data to third parties or the government, KAPDACLICK will do so.
  4. KAPDACLICK implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to any unlawful interception of Personal Information.But, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

## 2. Shared Personal Information

You are needed to submit your data at the time of making an online purchase on Website. KAPDACLICK uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the data that you share with KAPDACLICK is transferred and shared with this third party payment gateway operator.

“The said operator may also have access to your online purchase history/details that you make from the Website”.

Extremely sensitive data like your credit card details are transacted upon secure sites of approved payment gateways which are digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care as per current technology.

You are advised, however, that internet technology is not 100% safe and you should be discrete on using the same.

## 3. Links to Third Party Websites

The Website provides third-party advertisements and links to other websites. KAPDACLICK does not provide any Personal Information to these third-party websites or advertisers.

KAPDACLICK will have links to other websites ("Linked Site") on Website which are run by third parties and are not controlled by, or affiliated to, or associated with, KAPDACLICK unless expressly specified on Website. KAPDACLICK is not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by you from any Linked Site.

Similarly, KAPDACLICK does not make any representations concerning the privacy policies of such third parties or terms of use of such websites, nor does KAPDACLICK control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other materials available on such websites. The inclusion or exclusion does not imply any endorsement by KAPDACLICK of the website, the website's provider, or the data on the website. The data provided by you to such third party websites shall be governed in accordance with the privacy policies of such websites and it is recommended that you review the privacy policy on any such websites prior to using such websites.

These third-party websites and advertisers may use technology to send ads that appear on the Website directly to your browser. In such cases, the third party websites or advertisers automatically receive your IP address. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content.

KAPDACLICK does not have access to/control over cookies or other features that such third party websites and advertisers may use, and the data practices of these third-party websites and advertisers are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more data about their privacy practices.

## 4. Security

KAPDACLICK seeks to ensure the security, privacy and integrity of your Personal Information and to guard your Personal Information against unauthorized access/disclosure and unauthorized alteration.  
For this purpose, KAPDACLICK adopts internal reviews of the data collection, processing and storage practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access to systems where KAPDACLICK stores your Personal Information.

KAPDACLICK is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive your Personal Information.

The Website also linked to many other sites and we are not/shall be not responsible for their privacy policies or practices as it is beyond our control.

Nevertheless anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, KAPDACLICK shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of your Personal Information, if such damage, misuse or loss  is attributable to a Force Majeure Event (as defined below).

A " **Force Majeure Event** " shall mean any event that is beyond the reasonable control of KAPDACLICK and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer data and storage device, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption, etc.

## 5. Disclosure

KAPDACLICK will use data only in correspondence with the Policy under which the data was gathered unless we have received explicit authorization.

  1. KAPDACLICK may disclose any data KAPDACLICK may have about you (including your identity) if KAPDACLICK determines that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint about your use of the Website, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) KAPDACLICK's rights or property, or the rights or property of users of the Website, including KAPDACLICK's customers.
  2. KAPDACLICK reserves the right at all times to disclose any data that KAPDACLICK deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.
  3. KAPDACLICK also may disclose your data when KAPDACLICK determines that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging data with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes.

You acknowledge and agree that KAPDACLICK may preserve any communication by you with KAPDACLICK through the Website or any Service, and may also disclose such data if required to do so by law or if KAPDACLICK determines that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  1. comply with legal process;
  2. enforce this Policy;
  3. respond to claims that any such data violates the rights of others;
  4. protect the rights, property or personal safety of KAPDACLICK, its employees, users of, or visitors to, the Website, and the public.

## 6. User Discretion

You can decide not to provide data and in these cases, if the data needed is classified as compulsory, you will be unable to access of that part of the services or content.

  1. You can update your Personal Information on a normal basis. When you update data, KAPDACLICK will keep a copy of prior version for its records.
  2. KAPDACLICK may, if you choose, send advertisement mailers to you at your given address.
  3.  You have the choice to opt-out of this mailer by selecting unsubscribed link attached to the e-mail.
  4. KAPDACLICK respects your privacy and if you do not want to receive e-mail or other communications from KAPDACLICK, please report to KAPDACLICK at  customersupport@kapdaclick.com 
  5. If you do not want KAPDACLICK to use Personal Information that KAPDACLICK to you, please report to KAPDACLICK at customersupport@kapdaclick.com

  * 'Help' option of toolbar on your browsers will show you how to avoid your browser from accepting new cookies.
  * How to have the browser tell you when and how to disable cookies or you receive a new cookie.
  * You can disable similar data used by browser add-ons, by changing the add-on's settings or accessing Website of its manufacturer.
  * But, as cookies allow you to take benefit of some of Website's features, some of Website's contents and services may not function right, if your cookies are not enabled. So, It is prefered that you leave cookies on.
  *  For example, if you reject KAPDACLICK's cookies, you will be unable to add products to your cart, proceed to checkout, avail KAPDACLICK's services or  download any of KAPDACLICK's content that need you to log in.

## 7. General Provisions

By visiting Website, you have agreed to terms set in this Policy. This Policy should be at all times read along with the Terms of Use of the Website.

The Policy applies to all data that KAPDACLICK has regarding you, unless stated otherwise. acknowledge

By using Website and content, products and services given on Website, you accept that your Personal Information gathered by Website may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed  in any country. You admit that in certain countries or certain activities, the collection, storage, transfer and processing of your data may be done by trusted third party agents or sellers of KAPDACLICK like credit card processors, communication services,  web hosting providers and web analytic providers, to help KAPDACLICK in preparing certain functions.

“ **KAPDACLICK may make changes to this Policy, from time to time at KAPDACLICK's sole discretion or on account of changes in law** ”.

KAPDACLICK will not oppress your rights under this Policy without your explicit permission.

KAPDACLICK may e-mail timely reminders of conditions and notices, unless you have instructed

KAPDACLICK not to, but you should visit the Website regularly to find latest changes.

Nevertheless, KAPDACLICK shall not be required to notify you of any differences made to this Policy.

Revised Policy shall be made accessible on Website. Your extended use of Website, following alterations to the Policy, will represent your acceptance of the said changes.

If you visit the Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and Terms of Use. In summation to the preceding, any conflicts arising under this Policy shall be regulated by the laws of India.

## 8. Grievance Officer

In agreement with rules of data Technology Act 2000, the contact details of the Grievance Officer who can be contacted for any concerns and complaints including those referring to breach of KAPDACLICK’s Term of Offer For Sale, Terms of Use and other policies are issued as under:

**Email address** : [grievanceofficer@gmail.com](mailto:grievanceofficer@gmail.com)
